Finding Aid for Carol June Bradley Music Librarianship Oral History Recordings, 1973-1988
State University of New York at Buffalo. Music Library
- Cassettes, 1973-1988, I.; Cassette 1-135
  - Heyer, Anna Harriet, 1909-2002: Part 1, 1980-03-23, 1 audiocassette; Duration: 00:59:19 Location of recording: Fort Worth (Tex.) Type of tape: Maxell UDXLII C60 stereo. (Box 2, Audiocassette 49)
    Preservation archival master files: ubmu0076_049_01_am.wav, ubmu0076_049_02_am.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0076_049_01_sc.mp3, ubmu0076_049_02_sc.mp3
  - Heyer, Anna Harriet, 1909-2002: Part 2, 1980-03-23, 1 audiocassette; Duration: 00:22:09 Location of recording: Fort Worth (Tex.) Type of tape: Maxell UDXLII C60 stereo. Side 2 is blank. (Box 2, Audiocassette 50)
    Preservation archival master files: ubmu0076_050_01_am.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0076_050_01_sc.mp3
  - Heyer, Anna Harriet, 1909-2002: Part 3, 1980-03-23, 1 audiocassette; Duration: 01:01:37 Location of recording: Fort Worth (Tex.) Type of tape: Maxell UDXLII C60 stereo. (Box 2, Audiocassette 51)
    Preservation archival master files: ubmu0076_051_01_am.wav, ubmu0076_051_02_am.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0076_051_01_sc.mp3, ubmu0076_051_02_sc.mp3
  - Hinrichsen, Evelyn Merrell, 1981-10-28, 1 audiocassette; Duration: 01:03:32 Location of recording: New York (N.Y.) Type of tape: Maxell UDXLII C60 mono. (Box 2, Audiocassette 52)
    Preservation archival master files: ubmu0076_052_01_am.wav, ubmu0076_052_02_am.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0076_052_01_sc.mp3, ubmu0076_052_02_sc.mp3
  - Hoch, Marian Hill: Part 1, 1981-06-09, 1 audiocassette; Duration: 01:01:49 Location of recording: Elyria (Ohio) Type of tape: Maxell UDXLII C60 stereo. (Box 2, Audiocassette 53)
    Preservation archival master files: ubmu0076_053_01_am.wav, ubmu0076_053_02_am.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0076_053_01_sc.mp3, ubmu0076_053_02_sc.mp3
  - Hoch, Marian Hill: Part 2, 1981-06-09, 1 audiocassette; Duration: 01:03:24 Location of recording: Elyria (Ohio) Type of tape: Maxell UDXLII C60 mono. (Box 2, Audiocassette 54)
    Preservation archival master files: ubmu0076_054_01_am.wav, ubmu0076_054_02_am.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0076_054_01_sc.mp3, ubmu0076_054_02_sc.mp3
  - Hoch, Marian Hill: Part 3, 1981-06-09, 1 audiocassette; Duration: 01:03:22 Location of recording: Elyria (Ohio) Type of tape: Maxell UDXLII C60 mono. (Box 2, Audiocassette 55)
    Preservation archival master files: ubmu0076_055_01_am.wav, ubmu0076_055_02_am.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0076_055_01_sc.mp3, ubmu0076_055_02_sc.mp3
  - Hoch, Marian Hill: Part 4, 1981-06-09--1981-06-10, 1 audiocassette; Duration: 00:51:45 Location of recording: Elyria (Ohio) Type of tape: Maxell UDXLII C60 mono. (Box 2, Audiocassette 56)
    Preservation archival master files: ubmu0076_056_01_am.wav, ubmu0076_056_02_am.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0076_056_01_sc.mp3, ubmu0076_056_02_sc.mp3
  - Hoch, Marian Hill: Part 5, 1981-06-10, 1 audiocassette; Duration: 00:37:27 Location of recording: Elyria (Ohio) Type of tape: Maxell UDXLII C60 mono. (Box 2, Audiocassette 57)
    Preservation archival master files: ubmu0076_057_01_am.wav, ubmu0076_057_02_am.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0076_057_01_sc.mp3, ubmu0076_057_02_sc.mp3
  - Kownatsky, Harry L.: Part 1, 1986-12-04, 1 audiocassette; Duration: 01:02:21 Location of recording: Philadelphia (Pa.) Type of tape: Maxell XLII S 60 mono. (Box 2, Audiocassette 58)
    Preservation archival master files: ubmu0076_058_01_am.wav, ubmu0076_058_02_am.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0076_058_01_sc.mp3, ubmu0076_058_02_sc.mp3
  - Kownatsky, Harry L.: Part 2, 1986-12-04, 1 audiocassette; Duration: 00:15:19 Location of recording: Philadelphia (Pa.) Type of tape: Maxell XLII S 60 mono. (Box 2, Audiocassette 59)
    Preservation archival master files: ubmu0076_059_01_am.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0076_059_01_sc.mp3
  - Kretzschmar, Florence and McCullough Helena Gervais: Part 1, 1982-08-17--1982-08-18, 1 audiocassette; Duration: 00:58:02 Location of recording: Detroit (Mich.); Oak Park (Ill.) Type of tape: Maxell UDXLII C60 mono. McCullough (Side B) continued on Tape 81. Side 2 is blank. (Box 2, Audiocassette 60)
    Preservation archival master files: ubmu0076_060_01_am.wav, ubmu0076_060_02_am.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0076_060_01_sc.mp3, ubmu0076_060_02_sc.mp3
  - Lay, Catherine Nimitz: Part 1, 1978-06-16, 1 audiocassette; Duration: 00:56:31 Location of recording: Wellfleet (Mass.) Type of tape: Maxell UDXLII C60 stereo. Numbering from insert (Box 2, Audiocassette 61)
    Preservation archival master files: ubmu0076_061_01_am.wav, ubmu0076_061_02_am.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0076_061_01_sc.mp3, ubmu0076_061_02_sc.mp3
  - Lay, Catherine Nimitz: Part 2, 1978-06-16, 1 audiocassette; Duration: 01:03:13 Location of recording: Wellfleet (Mass.) Type of tape: Maxell UDXLII C60 stereo. Numbering from insert (Box 2, Audiocassette 62)
    Preservation archival master files: ubmu0076_062_01_am.wav, ubmu0076_062_02_am.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0076_062_01_sc.mp3, ubmu0076_062_02_sc.mp3
  - Lay, Catherine Nimitz: Part 3, 1978-06-16, 1 audiocassette; Duration: 00:23:20 Location of recording: Wellfleet (Mass.) Type of tape: Maxell UDXLII C60 stereo. Numbering from insert. Side 2 is blank. (Box 2, Audiocassette 63)
    Preservation archival master files: ubmu0076_063_01_am.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0076_063_01_sc.mp3
  - Lichtenwanger, William, 1915-2000: Part 1, 1981-03-15, 1 audiocassette; Duration: 00:56:03 Location of recording: Berkeley Springs (W. Va.) Type of tape: Maxell UDXLII C60 mono. (Box 2, Audiocassette 64)
    Preservation archival master files: ubmu0076_064_01_am.wav, ubmu0076_064_02_am.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0076_064_01_sc.mp3, ubmu0076_064_02_sc.mp3
  - Lichtenwanger, William, 1915-2000: Part 2, 1981-03-15, 1 audiocassette; Duration: 00:55:35 Location of recording: Berkeley Springs (W. Va.) Type of tape: Maxell UDXLII C60 mono. (Box 2, Audiocassette 65)
    Preservation archival master files: ubmu0076_065_01_am.wav, ubmu0076_065_02_am.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0076_065_01_sc.mp3, ubmu0076_065_02_sc.mp3
  - Lichtenwanger, William, 1915-2000: Part 3, 1981-03-15, 1 audiocassette; Duration: 00:49:56 Location of recording: Berkeley Springs (W. Va.) Type of tape: Maxell UDXLII C60 mono. (Box 2, Audiocassette 66)
    Preservation archival master files: ubmu0076_066_01_am.wav, ubmu0076_066_02_am.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0076_066_01_sc.mp3, ubmu0076_066_02_sc.mp3
  - Lichtenwanger, William, 1915-2000: Part 4, 1981-03-16, 1 audiocassette; Duration: 00:55:49 Location of recording: Berkeley Springs (W. Va.) Type of tape: Maxell UDXLII C60 stereo. (Box 2, Audiocassette 67)
    Preservation archival master files: ubmu0076_067_01_am.wav, ubmu0076_067_02_am.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0076_067_01_sc.mp3, ubmu0076_067_02_sc.mp3
  - Lichtenwanger, William, 1915-2000: Part 5, 1981-03-16, 1 audiocassette; Duration: 00:57:09 Location of recording: Berkeley Springs (W. Va.) Type of tape: Maxell UDXLII C60 mono. (Box 2, Audiocassette 68)
    Preservation archival master files: ubmu0076_068_01_am.wav, ubmu0076_068_02_am.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0076_068_01_sc.mp3, ubmu0076_068_02_sc.mp3
  - Lichtenwanger, William, 1915-2000: Part 6, 1981-03-16, 1 audiocassette; Duration: 00:52:03 Location of recording: Berkeley Springs (W. Va.) Type of tape: Maxell UDXLII C60 mono. (Box 2, Audiocassette 69)
    Preservation archival master files: ubmu0076_069_01_am.wav, ubmu0076_069_02_am.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0076_069_01_sc.mp3, ubmu0076_069_02_sc.mp3
  - Lichtenwanger, William, 1915-2000: Part 7, 1981-03-16, 1 audiocassette; Duration: 00:56:11 Location of recording: Berkeley Springs (W. Va.) Type of tape: Maxell UDXLII C60 mono. (Box 2, Audiocassette 70)
    Preservation archival master files: ubmu0076_070_01_am.wav, ubmu0076_070_02_am.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0076_070_01_sc.mp3, ubmu0076_070_02_sc.mp3
  - Lichtenwanger, William, 1915-2000: Part 8, 1981-03-16, 1 audiocassette; Duration: 00:54:40 Location of recording: Berkeley Springs (W. Va.) Type of tape: Maxell UDXLII C60 mono. Note on case: Can't hear ... try other cassette (Box 2, Audiocassette 71)
    Preservation archival master files: ubmu0076_071_01_am.wav, ubmu0076_071_02_am.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0076_071_01_sc.mp3, ubmu0076_071_02_sc.mp3
  - Lichtenwanger, William, 1915-2000: Part 9, 1981-03-16, 1 audiocassette; Duration: 00:54:11 Location of recording: Berkeley Springs (W. Va.) Type of tape: Maxell UDXLII C60 mono. (Box 2, Audiocassette 72)
    Preservation archival master files: ubmu0076_072_01_am.wav, ubmu0076_072_02_am.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0076_072_01_sc.mp3, ubmu0076_072_02_sc.mp3
  - Lichtenwanger, William, 1915-2000: Part 10, 1981-03-16--1981-03-17, 1 audiocassette; Duration: 00:54:37 Location of recording: Berkeley Springs (W. Va.) Type of tape: Maxell UDXLII C60 mono. (Box 2, Audiocassette 73)
    Preservation archival master files: ubmu0076_073_01_am.wav, ubmu0076_073_02_am.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0076_073_01_sc.mp3, ubmu0076_073_02_sc.mp3
  - Lichtenwanger, William, 1915-2000: Part 11, 1981-03-17, 1 audiocassette; Duration: 00:55:19 Location of recording: Berkeley Springs (W. Va.) Type of tape: Maxell UDXLII C60 mono. (Box 2, Audiocassette 74)
    Preservation archival master files: ubmu0076_074_01_am.wav, ubmu0076_074_02_am.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0076_074_01_sc.mp3, ubmu0076_074_02_sc.mp3
  - Lichtenwanger, William, 1915-2000: Part 12, 1981-03-17, 1 audiocassette; Duration: 00:53:30 Location of recording: Berkeley Springs (W. Va.) Type of tape: Maxell UDXLII C60 mono. (Box 2, Audiocassette 75)
    Preservation archival master files: ubmu0076_075_01_am.wav, ubmu0076_075_02_am.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0076_075_01_sc.mp3, ubmu0076_075_02_sc.mp3
  - Lichtenwanger, William, 1915-2000: Part 13, 1981-03-17, 1 audiocassette; Duration: 00:13:31 Location of recording: Berkeley Springs (W. Va.) Type of tape: Maxell UDXLII C60 mono. Side 2 is blank. (Box 2, Audiocassette 76)
    Preservation archival master files: ubmu0076_076_01_am.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0076_076_01_sc.mp3
  - Ludden, Bennet: Part 1, 1985-12-06, 1 audiocassette; Duration: 01:01:03 Location of recording: New York (N.Y.) Type of tape: Maxell UDXLII 60 stereo. Copyright and literary rights belong to the Music Library Association (Box 2, Audiocassette 77)
    Preservation archival master files: ubmu0076_077_01_am.wav, ubmu0076_077_02_am.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0076_077_01_sc.mp3, ubmu0076_077_02_sc.mp3
  - Ludden, Bennet: Part 2, 1985-12-06, 1 audiocassette; Duration: 01:00:17 Location of recording: New York (N.Y.) Type of tape: Maxell UDXLII 60 stereo. Copyright and literary rights belong to the Music Library Association (Box 2, Audiocassette 78)
    Preservation archival master files: ubmu0076_078_01_am.wav, ubmu0076_078_02_am.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0076_078_01_sc.mp3, ubmu0076_078_02_sc.mp3
  - Ludden, Bennet: Part 3, 1985-12-06--1985-12-07, 1 audiocassette; Duration: 00:50:21 Location of recording: New York (N.Y.) Type of tape: Maxell UDXLII 60 stereo. Copyright and literary rights belong to the Music Library Association (Box 2, Audiocassette 79)
    Preservation archival master files: ubmu0076_079_01_am.wav, ubmu0076_079_02_am.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0076_079_01_sc.mp3, ubmu0076_079_02_sc.mp3
  - Ludden, Bennet: Part 4, 1985-12-07, 1 audiocassette; Duration: 00:57:44 Location of recording: New York (N.Y.) Type of tape: Maxell UDXLII 60 stereo. Copyright and literary rights belong to the Music Library Association (Box 2, Audiocassette 80)
    Preservation archival master files: ubmu0076_080_01_am.wav, ubmu0076_080_02_am.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0076_080_01_sc.mp3, ubmu0076_080_02_sc.mp3
  - McCullough, Helena Gervais: Part 2, 1982-08-18, 1 audiocassette; Duration: 00:56:08 Location of recording: Oak Park (Ill.) Type of tape: Maxell UDXLII C60 mono. Continuation of Tape 60 Side B (Box 2, Audiocassette 81)
    Preservation archival master files: ubmu0076_081_01_am.wav, ubmu0076_081_02_am.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0076_081_01_sc.mp3, ubmu0076_081_02_sc.mp3
  - Mestechin, Natalie and Schmitter, Elizabeth, 1973-06-30, 1973-10-02, 1 audiocassette; Duration: 01:01:29 Location of recording: San Francisco (Calif.); Northampton (Mass.) Type of tape: TDK C-60SD mono. Schmitter continued on Tape 106; Unclear if both interviews are on Side A or split between both sides (Box 2, Audiocassette 82)
    Preservation archival master files: ubmu0076_082_01_am.wav, ubmu0076_082_02_am.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0076_082_01_sc.mp3, ubmu0076_082_02_sc.mp3
  - Miller, Philip Lieson, 1906-1996: Part 1, 1974-06-08, 1 audiocassette; Duration: 01:03:12 Location of recording: New York (N.Y.) Type of tape: TDK SD C60 mono. (Box 2, Audiocassette 83)
    Preservation archival master files: ubmu0076_083_01_am.wav, ubmu0076_083_02_am.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0076_083_01_sc.mp3, ubmu0076_083_02_sc.mp3
  - Miller, Philip Lieson, 1906-1996: Part 2, 1974-06-08, 1 audiocassette; Duration: 00:59:44 Location of recording: New York (N.Y.) Type of tape: TDK SD C60 stereo. (Box 2, Audiocassette 84)
    Preservation archival master files: ubmu0076_084_01_am.wav, ubmu0076_084_02_am.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0076_084_01_sc.mp3, ubmu0076_084_02_sc.mp3
  - Miller, Philip Lieson, 1906-1996: Part 3, 1974-06-08, 1 audiocassette; Duration: 00:14:35 Location of recording: New York (N.Y.) Type of tape: TDK D C60 stereo. Side 2 is blank (Box 2, Audiocassette 85)
    Preservation archival master files: ubmu0076_085_01_am.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0076_085_01_sc.mp3
  - Miller, Philip Lieson, 1906-1996: Part 4, 1986-12-02, 1 audiocassette; Duration: 01:00:01 Location of recording: New York (N.Y.) Type of tape: Maxell XLIIS 60 stereo. Copyright and literary rights belong to the Music Library Association (Box 2, Audiocassette 86)
    Preservation archival master files: ubmu0076_086_01_am.wav, ubmu0076_086_02_am.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0076_086_01_sc.mp3, ubmu0076_086_02_sc.mp3
  - Miller, Philip Lieson, 1906-1996: Part 5, 1986-12-02, 1 audiocassette; Duration: 00:46:27 Location of recording: New York (N.Y.) Type of tape: Maxell UDXLII 60 stereo. Copyright and literary rights belong to the Music Library Association (Box 2, Audiocassette 87)
    Preservation archival master files: ubmu0076_087_01_am.wav, ubmu0076_087_02_am.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0076_087_01_sc.mp3, ubmu0076_087_02_sc.mp3
  - Miller, Philip Lieson, 1906-1996: Part 6, 1986-12-03, 1 audiocassette; Duration: 00:43:56 Location of recording: New York (N.Y.) Type of tape: Maxell UDXLII 60 stereo. Copyright and literary rights belong to the Music Library Association (Box 2, Audiocassette 88)
    Preservation archival master files: ubmu0076_088_01_am.wav, ubmu0076_088_02_am.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0076_088_01_sc.mp3, ubmu0076_088_02_sc.mp3
  - Myers, Kurtz: Part 1, 1981-02-13, 1 audiocassette; Duration: 00:53:29 Location of recording: New Haven (Conn.) Type of tape: Maxell UDXLII C60 mono. Recorded in New Haven Hotel, MLA 50th anniversary (Box 2, Audiocassette 89)
    Preservation archival master files: ubmu0076_089_01_am.wav, ubmu0076_089_02_am.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0076_089_01_sc.mp3, ubmu0076_089_02_sc.mp3
  - Myers, Kurtz: Part 2, 1981-02-13, 1 audiocassette; Duration: 00:57:45 Location of recording: New Haven (Conn.) Type of tape: Maxell UDXLII C60 mono. Recorded in New Haven Hotel, MLA 50th anniversary (Box 2, Audiocassette 90)
    Preservation archival master files: ubmu0076_090_01_am.wav, ubmu0076_090_02_am.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0076_090_01_sc.mp3, ubmu0076_090_02_sc.mp3
  - Myers, Kurtz: Part 3, 1981-02-13, 1 audiocassette; Duration: 00:31:46 Location of recording: New Haven (Conn.) Type of tape: Maxell UDXLII C60 mono. Side 2 is blank. Recorded in New Haven Hotel, MLA 50th anniversary (Box 2, Audiocassette 91)
    Preservation archival master files: ubmu0076_091_01_am.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0076_091_01_sc.mp3
  - O'Meara, Eva Judd: Part 1, 1973-06-11, 1 audiocassette; Duration: 00:56:18 Location of recording: New Haven (Conn.) Type of tape: BASF C60 stereo. (Box 2, Audiocassette 92)
    Preservation archival master files: ubmu0076_092_01_am.wav, ubmu0076_092_02_am.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0076_092_01_sc.mp3, ubmu0076_092_02_sc.mp3
  - O'Meara, Eva Judd: Part 2, 1973-06-11--1973-06-12, 1 audiocassette; Duration: 01:01:45 Location of recording: New Haven (Conn.) Type of tape: BASF C60 mono. (Box 2, Audiocassette 93)
    Preservation archival master files: ubmu0076_093_01_am.wav, ubmu0076_093_02_am.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0076_093_01_sc.mp3, ubmu0076_093_02_sc.mp3
  - O'Meara, Eva Judd: Part 3, 1973-06-12, 1 audiocassette; Duration: 01:00:19 Location of recording: New Haven (Conn.) Type of tape: BASF C60 mono. (Box 2, Audiocassette 94)
    Preservation archival master files: ubmu0076_094_01_am.wav, ubmu0076_094_02_am.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0076_094_01_sc.mp3, ubmu0076_094_02_sc.mp3
  - O'Meara, Eva Judd: Part 4, 1973-06-12, 1 audiocassette; Duration: 01:00:36 Location of recording: New Haven (Conn.) Type of tape: BASF C60 mono. (Box 2, Audiocassette 95)
    Preservation archival master files: ubmu0076_095_01_am.wav, ubmu0076_095_02_am.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0076_095_01_sc.mp3, ubmu0076_095_02_sc.mp3
  - O'Meara, Eva Judd: Part 5, 1973-06-12, 1 audiocassette; Duration: 00:18:45 Location of recording: New Haven (Conn.) Type of tape: BASF C60 mono. Side 2 is blank. (Box 2, Audiocassette 96)
    Preservation archival master files: ubmu0076_096_01_am.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0076_096_01_sc.mp3
  - Peterson, Melva: Part 1, 1988-07-21, 1 audiocassette; Duration: 01:03:32 Location of recording: New York (N.Y.) Type of tape: Maxell XLII S 60 mono. Copyright and literary rights belong to the Music Library Association (Box 3, Audiocassette 97)
    Preservation archival master files: ubmu0076_097_01_am.wav, ubmu0076_097_02_am.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0076_097_01_sc.mp3, ubmu0076_097_02_sc.mp3
  - Peterson, Melva: Part 2, 1988-07-21, 1 audiocassette; Duration: 01:02:43 Location of recording: New York (N.Y.) Type of tape: Maxell XLII S 60 mono. Copyright and literary rights belong to the Music Library Association (Box 3, Audiocassette 98)
    Preservation archival master files: ubmu0076_098_01_am.wav, ubmu0076_098_02_am.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0076_098_01_sc.mp3, ubmu0076_098_02_sc.mp3
  - Peterson, Melva: Part 3, 1988-07-21, 1 audiocassette; Duration: 01:00:35 Location of recording: New York (N.Y.) Type of tape: Maxell XLII S 60 mono. Copyright and literary rights belong to the Music Library Association (Box 3, Audiocassette 99)
    Preservation archival master files: ubmu0076_099_01_am.wav, ubmu0076_099_02_am.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0076_099_01_sc.mp3, ubmu0076_099_02_sc.mp3
  - Peterson, Melva: Part 4, 1988-07-21--1988-07-22, 1 audiocassette; Duration: 00:58:02 Location of recording: New York (N.Y.) Type of tape: Maxell XLII S 60 mono. Copyright and literary rights belong to the Music Library Association (Box 3, Audiocassette 100)
    Preservation archival master files: ubmu0076_100_01_am.wav, ubmu0076_100_02_am.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0076_100_01_sc.mp3, ubmu0076_100_02_sc.mp3
  - Peterson, Melva: Part 5, 1988-07-22, 1 audiocassette; Duration: 01:03:26 Location of recording: New York (N.Y.) Type of tape: Maxell XLII S 60 mono. Copyright and literary rights belong to the Music Library Association (Box 3, Audiocassette 101)
    Preservation archival master files: ubmu0076_101_01_am.wav, ubmu0076_101_02_am.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0076_101_01_sc.mp3, ubmu0076_101_02_sc.mp3
  - Peterson, Melva: Part 6, 1988-07-22, 1 audiocassette; Duration: 00:23:20 Location of recording: New York (N.Y.) Type of tape: Maxell XLII S 60 mono. Side 2 is blank. Copyright and literary rights belong to the Music Library Association (Box 3, Audiocassette 102)
    Preservation archival master files: ubmu0076_102_01_am.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0076_102_01_sc.mp3
  - Rogers, Mary: Part 1 1981-10-11, 1 audiocassette; Duration: 01:03:32 Location of recording: Washington (D.C.) Type of tape: Maxell UDXLII C60 mono. (Box 3, Audiocassette 103)
    Preservation archival master files: ubmu0076_103_01_am.wav, ubmu0076_103_02_am.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0076_103_01_sc.mp3, ubmu0076_103_02_sc.mp3
  - Rogers, Mary: Part 2, 1981-10-11, 1 audiocassette; Duration: 01:03:23 Location of recording: Washington (D.C.) Type of tape: Maxell UDXLII C60 mono. (Box 3, Audiocassette 104)
    Preservation archival master files: ubmu0076_104_01_am.wav, ubmu0076_104_02_am.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0076_104_01_sc.mp3, ubmu0076_104_02_sc.mp3
  - Rogers, Mary: Part 3, 1981-10-11, 1 audiocassette; Duration: 00:18:06 Location of recording: Washington (D.C.) Type of tape: Maxell UDXLII C60 mono. Side 2 is blank. (Box 3, Audiocassette 105)
    Preservation archival master files: ubmu0076_105_01_am.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0076_105_01_sc.mp3
  - Schmitter, Elizabeth: Part 2, 1973-10-02, 1 audiocassette; Duration: 00:54:28 Location of recording: Northampton (Mass.) Type of tape: TDK C-60SD mono. Continuation of Tape 82. Side 2 is blank. (Box 3, Audiocassette 106)
    Preservation archival master files: ubmu0076_106_01_am.wav, ubmu0076_106_02_am.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0076_106_01_sc.mp3, ubmu0076_106_02_sc.mp3
  - Smith, Carleton Sprague, 1905-1994: Part 1, 1974-07-09, 1 audiocassette; Duration: 00:59:36 Location of recording: New York (N.Y.) Type of tape: TDK SD C60 mono. Numbering from cassette label (Box 3, Audiocassette 107)
    Preservation archival master files: ubmu0076_107_01_am.wav, ubmu0076_107_02_am.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0076_107_01_sc.mp3, ubmu0076_107_02_sc.mp3
  - Smith, Carleton Sprague, 1905-1994: Part 2, 1974-07-09, 1 audiocassette; Duration: 01:01:21 Location of recording: New York (N.Y.) Type of tape: TDK D C60 stereo. Numbering from cassette label (Box 3, Audiocassette 108)
    Preservation archival master files: ubmu0076_108_01_am.wav, ubmu0076_108_02_am.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0076_108_01_sc.mp3, ubmu0076_108_02_sc.mp3
  - Smith, Carleton Sprague, 1905-1994: Part 3, 1974-07-10, 1 audiocassette; Duration: 01:02:36 Location of recording: New York (N.Y.) Type of tape: TDK D C60 mono. Bobst Library, NYU (Box 3, Audiocassette 109)
    Preservation archival master files: ubmu0076_109_01_am.wav, ubmu0076_109_02_am.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0076_109_01_sc.mp3, ubmu0076_109_02_sc.mp3
  - Smith, Carleton Sprague, 1905-1994: Part 4, 1974-07-10, 1 audiocassette; Duration: 00:54:25 Location of recording: New York (N.Y.) Type of tape: TDK SD C60 mono. Bobst Library, NYU (Box 3, Audiocassette 110)
    Preservation archival master files: ubmu0076_110_01_am.wav, ubmu0076_110_02_am.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0076_110_01_sc.mp3, ubmu0076_110_02_sc.mp3
  - Spivacke, Harold, 1904-1977: Part 1, 1974-04-09, 1 audiocassette; Duration: 00:54:23 Location of recording: Washington (D.C.) Type of tape: TDK C-60LN mono. (Box 3, Audiocassette 111)
    Preservation archival master files: ubmu0076_111_01_am.wav, ubmu0076_111_02_am.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0076_111_01_sc.mp3, ubmu0076_111_02_sc.mp3
  - Spivacke, Harold, 1904-1977: Part 2, 1974-04-09--1974-04-10, 1 audiocassette; Duration: 01:01:19 Location of recording: Washington (D.C.) Type of tape: TDK C-60LN mono. (Box 3, Audiocassette 112)
    Preservation archival master files: ubmu0076_112_01_am.wav, ubmu0076_112_02_am.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0076_112_01_sc.mp3, ubmu0076_112_02_sc.mp3